好了，你已经做完了。让我们看看
All right, you're done. Let's take a look
答案。删除实际上是很直接的。
at the solution. Delete is actually pretty straight forward.
再次注意以下我们几乎没有无用的
Note that once again we have almost useless
参数。S实际上引用了我们的选择尽管我们这的字符串实际上是Rs。
parameters. S actually refers to our selection while our
在删除中一个
strings here are actually our selection Rs. One
小问题是如果我们
little trickiness in delete is that if you actually
没有selection，则将删除全部的行。
put no selection in, it'll delete all the rows.
我仍然想确保我们通知这次改变。
I still want to make sure we notify the change.
我已经做了。
I've done the slide optimization here. It would be
一直通知改变是没问题的，但是我已经决定
fine to just notify the change always, but I've decided
如果没有行被删除，你那么我们应该
if no rows have been deleted, then we should
阻止这次通知。除非selection是null，
bother not notifying. Unless the selection is null, in which
这种情况下将删除全部的行，但是话说回来，
case we deleted all the rows, but again, it
通知改变是没问题的尽管
would be fine just to use notify change here even
没有行被删除。毕竟，意图是
if no rows are actually deleted. After all, the intention
被删除的行。再看，
was that rows would be deleted. Once again, let's take
让我们同情以下那些可能维护你代码的人，
pity on someone who might have to maintain your code, and change
将那些默认的参数名改成
these default parameter names to something
更有用的如selection和selectionargs。
more useful like selection and selectionargs.
否则，update看起来几乎了delete一模一行。
Other than that, update looks almost exactly like delete. Once
我们返回更新影响的行数。
again, we are returning the number of rows impacted by
如果没有行被影响，我们不担心通知。
the update, and we don't bother notifying if no rows
既然我们已经结束了实现update和delete，我们
were impacted. Now that we've finished writing update and delete, we
能够回去测试provider，并且加一些测试。
can go back to test provider and add some tests.
首先，我们删除delete.db，最后的测试并不依赖于provider。
First, let's remove test delete.db, the last test that doesn't depend
现在，让我们加一个测试用来删除
on the provider. Instead, let's have a test that deletes
全部的记录并且确保确实删除了。
all the records and checks to make sure they're actually deleted.
记住，传递一个空的查询实际上是删除了
Remember, passing a null query actually deletes all of the
表中的全部记录。因此非常简单只需要传一个
records in a table. So this is really straight-forward, just passing
null。因为我们依赖我们删除的数据库，
nulls. Since we're depending on the database for our deletes, it's
我们是否真实测试过delete函数并不重要，
not all that particularly important that we actually test the delete
尽管在以后加入这些也可以。
functions, although it would be nice to add that later on.
我们想现在加入的原因是想确保
The reason we'd want to add it is to make sure that
我们的限制是合法的。并且我们曾经做过删除，
our constraints are valid. And once we're done doing the deletes,
我们检查现在没有一行剩下。
we check to make sure that there are no rows left.
注意在我们删除location元组之前我们已经删除weather元组了，
Note that we have to delete weather entry before we delete location
因为我们在数据库中存在一个限制，那就是
entry, because you've got constraints in the database that prevent weather entry
如果location元组不存在，那么weather元组也不能存在，并且
from existing if location entries do not also exist and would also
避免删除location元组。因此我们查看是否确实
prevent the deletion of those entries. So let's check to see whether
工作了。好了，通过了。这是好消息。现在我们能
that actually works. All right, that passes. Good news. Now we can
添加同样的测试到最后确保我们
add the same test to the end to make sure we can
在最后能删除全部的行，并仍然能工作。
delete all of the rows at the end and it still works.
正如我们看到的，他们也通过了。因此我们现在知道我们已经
And as you can see, they still pass. So now we know we've
在运行测试前和后都删除了记录。现在，让我们试着
deleted records before and after running tests. Now, let's try
更新。我们将只做location的更新。
that update. We'll do just an update of the location.
再一次，我们以删除全部记录为开始，然后添加一条
Again, let's start by deleting all records and inserting a
我们想更新的记录。一件好事情是
record that we want to update. One of the nice things about
contentValues是我们使用了一个复制构造函数来复制他们。
content values is you can actually copy them using a
之后，我们能添加我们
copy constructor. After that, we can add the ID we
想更新的ID，然后添加我们
want to update and then put the name of the city
想更新的城市的名字。在这里，从North Pole
we want to update it to. In this case, from North Pole
更新成Santa's Village。然后，我们调用update。
to Santa's Village. And then, finally, we call update.
注意，我们实际上更新了一个记录，
Assert that we've actually updated exactly one record as
这正是我们想要的，然后我们做了一个查询，
we'd expect, and then do a query on that,
测试我们的游标，确保这次更新是生效的。
validating our cursor, making sure that our update actually works.
最后，我们关闭我们的游标。全部
And then finally, we close our cursor. It all
都看起来很好。我们看到他确实运行了，
looks pretty good. And let's see that it actually runs,
做了正确的事。我们测试通过了。
and does the right thing. And our tests pass.
因此，我们已经证明了我们能更新，删除，插入，
So, we've now proved that we can update, delete, insert,
和查询，并且全部都已经测试过。
and query and all this is fully tested.
换句话说，我们应用的主体
In other words, the bones of our application
已经结束，只需要将我们的UI连接上即可。
are finished, just waiting to attach our UI.
让我们开始将我们的UI连接上。
Let's go through and attach some of our UI.